Let's go, GURU CHANNEL GO!
Yes, today
I think the background is different, but I'm not going home until I get a score of 95 or higher on the red paper today.
I can't go home until I get a score over 95 on the red paper today! Yay!
This is my first karaoke project. But Yoko, first of all, it's been a long time since I've done karaoke. Is that so? I haven't gone to karaoke for a long time!
How long has it been? A year, a year, six months? I haven't eaten in six months to a year. Are you seriously worried? Yes, I am worried.
Because I don't have akapella. I don't bother to do orchestra with red percussion, so I just play the sound.
Have you ever done it? Yes, to begin with. I did it once quite a while ago. It was when I came with friends.
I got a really low score. Really. Was it something to do with timing? Or the sound?
I mean, there's timing, and you have to imagine the sound as you sing.
So I didn't have time to shuffle around. I'm too busy trying to match the notes. I see. The audience is still waiting for me.
Let's get a 95 and go home. Let's go home. Okay, let's start the video!
This time, I'm wearing D-Holic's costume.
Order?
Which one do I start with?
At first,
What about the impossible, doable, or doable?
I mean..,
No? First lap?
Let's try a first rap.
I'm singing, after all,
I'll just have to do my best.
Hey, hey.
Huh.
Yeah.
This one?
...
HAHAHA
rename
Smile
Magirania
Terrible and sad aroma
Yuck!
By this time tomorrow
I wonder where you are
I wonder who you're thinking of
You are always gonna be my love
Even if I fall in love again with someone someday
I remember to love you taught me how
Your love is gonna be the one
Now it's still a sad love song
Till I can sing a new song
You are always gonna be my love
Even if I fall in love with someone else again someday
I remember to fall in love
You tell me how
You are always gonna be my love
Still sad about this song
Now forever
Forever
Oh, my God.
I guess that means I have to practice.
But it'll be nice if Momochan comes to her first live performance.
I'm not a Cinderella boy.
You're right.
Wait, I don't get it.
I don't know. I really don't.
But my mind can't keep up with my body
It's so simple.
If you're a manIf you're a man.
Even more so.
Even less so if you're a woman.
What? It's a little...
It's a bit Cinderella-ish.
Turn the screw, don't make me cry in your arms
I hate cigarettes... that you pretend not to notice and leave them on.
It's nice, isn't it?
Maybe it's a little late for that.
I don't seem to mind.
You know, I make love sometimes.
Let me be mean to you.
At least lie to me.
Next time, you'll have to be better.
Oh, that's not easy.
But, you know, I've got my fists on it... a little bit.
But, you know, just the rust. It fits.
I'll pick the one that fits. Take away my stubbornness.
Don't make me cry in your arms
I was cheating on you.
Hey, ah...
Ha-ha-ha.
Wait, wait, wait. Not at all.
Was it bad at the end? But you know what?
You had the chorus.
It was right on!
You're not wrong.
Wait a minute...
What's the score?
It's a little bit bad, isn't it?
Yeah...
Ew.
Heh heh heh.
I've never taken a picture of Yuuko before.
Oh, my God, that's terrible.
Maybe you can sing something you want to sing? Like singing? So we'll go out at night.
Oh, wow.
It's on.
It's wine, really.
It really is.
It's wine.
Yes, it is.
Wow, great.
It's all falling now.
It's been a long time, you know.
It's nice.
That's a really beautiful scope.
It's the timing, isn't it?
If the timing is off, it might sound off.
It's good.
No?
Oh, it's good, right?
It works, doesn't it? Did it work?
It looked good.
Ahhh...
That's Maripace's way of singing.
Let's try singing along with the melody a little more.
That's why it's a cappella.
I'm sorry.
I'll try my best.
I think 95 is a little too high.I think 95 is a little too high.
But you know what?
One more try
Wait a minute... is there anything?
It's hard, isn't it?
Take my box.
Let me go.
But you know what?
The rhythm is so slow.
Minshu, please sing the solo without your name.
Go ahead.
Okay, then.
If it rains
I invite you and the wind
Find the little flowers that come pouring down
Look up at the sky with no name
I want to walk everywhere with you
If the stars shine in the night sky
I'll remember you before anyone else
If only one wish could reach the light
I'd close my eyes and go to sleep
When the time comes
I want to call your name
I wish I could say your name
I'll always call your name
Your beautiful name
Your beautiful name.
Hey, isn't it funny?
It's funny.
You seem a little strict. Because, Yoko, don't you usually get 99 points for this?
Well, I'm off to the Orpheus.
I have to go home soon.
That's right. Let's hurry. Let's hurry.
Orphans' tears Love bears our sorrows, can it be strong?
You're all mine, can you hear me? The sky sings the rules
All that remains in the sound of strife is only sorrow
What will the strong see in the shards of their dreams
Orphans to the skies
Now we set sail on a ship of hope
You're on my mind In this moment the sky sings Blues
Orphens, you who wander and wave your hands
I knew what it meant to fight
Love of my mind
Singing about love in this time
Is it good?
I think we probably went well.
Let's work a little harder.
Thank you for watching.
People can be kind to each other when they know sorrow.
Peace of mind, can you hear me?
The sky sings, love sings, I sing to you
Blues
Yeah, all night, in this moment
The sky sings, Blues
All of us, together
In your hands, there's a future that depicts freedom
Love on my mind
Ruth
I think I got it.
Did it go?
Please do.Please.
Did you get it?
Whoo!
Yeah!
That's great!
I got 97.332!
Oh, ONE PIECE!
No, no, no.
Lately ONE PIECE.
No, no, no, no.
I do like it, but...
Well, I sing A.M.E.Y.O.R. by ONE CLOCK
yeah i softly whisper tonight
tonight
you are my angel
I love you, yeah
We are one tonight
♪ I'm thinking of you
The way I feel for you
The day we met
Was the first momentous day for both of us.
And today
Is the second most memorable day of our lives.
Oh, isn't this so nice?
When you're around, I'm always by your side.
No matter what you say, I'll always think of you
I promise you now and forever
Wherever You Are
Hey, that's impossible, I can't go to karaoke anymore.
Yes, so I cleared Momochan.
But, Yoko definitely cleared it, too.
Vibrato was also beeped.
Maybe she's a person who can't do it without any sound. Maybe he has a terrible sense of rhythm.
That's for sure.
You've lost your sense of rhythm many times, so now you're going to have to play with sound interruptions.
I think it's the sound effects.
Miche and I, and Obako, we really get 99 centimeters for the sound division,
Ninety.
So, I thought I could do it.
That's why I thought I could do it.
I never got 99.
It was more than 10 centimeters lower.
I hope to be able to try my hand at sound splitting someday.
So thank you for watching.
If you like the video, please give it a high rating, comment and subscribe to the channel.
Bye bye.